Hello friends, welcome to
your own channel Latest Shayari.
Friends, here in India's healthcare
sector, healthcare in the sense,
healthcare sector and health insurance
sector, there has been some dispute right now, which has happened due to
Kuwait. Now
what do you think about it, the whole world is
in focus, HDFC Life, Relige
Technova and New India Assurance, etc.,
all your life insurance stocks are
now in focus. 2 hours ago, the news came on
Moneycontrol, so I have
brought that news in front of you, so we
will talk about it, so what is the news, will
we get some reaction on this
or not, let's see, in front of you, this
second fast of 2019, there has been tension between
hospital and insurance, that is,
between hospital and insurance companies,
and the second, the
remaining settlement here, which is still
pending, is one lakh
71 thousand flames, which is still
in waiting, which is its
chapter and  If there is a dispute in the insurance company,
what will happen now? It remains to be seen here
how they manage it. So, it has become clear
here that the
health care companies, these health
insurance companies, are
in a lot of focus, in which a lot of upheaval can happen due to this
cover, this can happen somewhere or the other.
If there is a problem in any company,
then keep in mind that big companies do
not get caught as quickly as small companies can get caught quickly.
So let's see
which stock is your focus, so HDFC Life
Insurance will be your focus, similarly
in Lombard General Insurance, if
New India Assurance Company Limited will be
in your focus, Religare Enterprises will be
in your focus,
you will be focused on Advance Finance Services and
SBI Life Insurance Company will be in more focus,
these stocks will be in focus, so keep in
mind, trade carefully, if
you have clear holdings, then you should take
care of that building.
So first we are going to put each and every detail in front of you, so that
we can know
which stocks are cheap in these stocks,
if there is
any news on shed tractor, this  If there is negative news then
we came to know later that this negative news
takes us to the post, if there is some
controversy here then this news will
not be for the insurance sector,
I have said that due to this the controversy
increases, if the controversy increases due to them then
it is going to come in focus, so there will be a
lot of turmoil here,
but before that we prepare,
if you have it, then you can see it, it does
not mean that
you should know this, so
here you will see the periodic table of HDFC Life
Insurance, Shilpi
Vishwam, there is
no need to write the rest of the details of all the companies, the rates which are behind,
so here the rates are very high, the
stock SBI
Life Insurance Company Peer Versus Pe is
1402, keep in mind it is a little
less here, but here the footer
cannot be very expensive, it is 13 to 14 points more expensive
here, this stock is from
our industry,
nothing is known about it, there is glass, the pressure is
not known, so leave it, it
is Religare Enterprises  Leave that too, I do
n't know the place for its capital, India
Gold is the cheapest stock, period 16 is
you, Nifty is 0.20 lighter, so friends, there is a lot of
interest here, the piece is very cheap, so it
seems that you may be hit less,
if it is, then the face has been
worse for a long time, this is 43.70
copy Anshu, the industry is 59.2 and the
interest is shameless, at least it is less, isn't it, what do you have to do,
see, when
you get this news in the market, if tomorrow, when the news
channels tell you that this news is
negative, then brother, these issues may get hit, otherwise, if
this news has come, then I felt that it is
important to tell you, Varal, you should read this link which has come on the
healthcare sector, on the health
insurance sector,
once on this link, that is, read the news that has come here once
and understand that there is
tension between the hospital and the insurance company, and if this dispute
increases, then it will affect the stocks, this
dispute is when the stocks etc. become serious, when the dispute between these two
deepens, right?  Till then this
stock may be hit, only till then this news
will be very negative
for the stock, otherwise there is nothing to be afraid of right now,
see right now it is at least around 10 lakhs,
right, a lot of that
they set a flame, they have to
search, but right now the total of 1 lakh 70 thousand
is there, so
something happens on them, by the
way this news comes, so keep in mind that if you
know the news then you should react only on the news,
it is not necessary that you should believe it, there is
no need for that, when
something is told to you,
if you have been told about it in
full detail then you should
give your reaction on it, otherwise there is
no need to give any reaction so quickly, right,
remember that
among all the insurance companies, two companies are much
better, one is Yours Lo White General
Insurance Company and the other is New India
Insurance Company, so see, these two stocks are
very different, the people there are
from the insurance staff, so
both these stocks can be affected, keep in mind, so if
you liked this video  If it is decided then you must
subscribe to this channel and now give
me permission to watch the video, thank you very much.